http://www.drpt.virginia.gov/privacy-statement/

Website Privacy Statement
The Virginia Department of Rail and Public Transportation (DRPT) is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors. Following are DRPT’s internet privacy practices, which may be amended at any time without notice.
Virginia LawsDRPT protects its records in accordance with applicable Virginia and federal law including, but not limited to, the Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act and the Virginia Freedom of Information Act. Any web pages that appear after navigating away from the DRPT website are controlled by a different agency or entity, whose practices are not under DRPT's control and for which DRPT is not responsible.
Essential Technical Information Collected and How it is UsedDRPT endeavors to collect only the minimum amount of information needed to provide services. DRPT will automatically collect and store the following essential technical information about your visit to the DRPT website:
The Internet domain and IP address from the device you used to access the website;
The type of browser and operating system you used;
The date and time you visited the website;
The pages visited; and
If you linked from another website, the address of that website.
The information collected is used to improve the content of DRPT’s web services and to help DRPT understand how people are using its website. DRPT analyzes this data to continually improve the value of the content on its website, the website’s functionality and to diagnose problems with DRPT’s servers.
If you send DRPT an e-mail message, it will collect the e-mail address and contents of the message, including audio, video, and graphic information or documentation you send. DRPT uses your e-mail address to respond to your request.
The only personal information DRPT collects is volunteered directly from individuals who subscribe to its services or participate in surveys. Collecting personal information is necessary for DRPT to deliver the services requested. Personal information collected, retained, and used is in DRPT’s judgment essential to administer its business and to provide products, services and other opportunities requested by DRPT’s customers.
CookiesWhen you visit a website and request information, the site's server sends the request to you and then breaks the connection. The connection does not resume again until you perform another action. To ensure that DRPT maintains a connection between its server and your computer, DRPT uses a standard technology called a "cookie", which is placed on your computer automatically unless your browser is not configured to "accept" cookies. A cookie is a very small amount of data that is sent from DRPT’s server to your computer's hard drive. In addition, cookies allow DRPT to save the information that you input while progressing through an online transaction. If your browser is not configured to "accept" cookies, you will still be able to access the static information on DRPT’s website, but you will not be able to use certain features, such as DRPT’s online transactions.
Restrictions on the Disclosure of Customer InformationDRPT does not share, sell or trade its subscribers' information to any outside company or organization. It does not reveal specific information about subscribers or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use, except as required by the Virginia Freedom of Information Act or other law.
Protection of Information via Established Security ProceduresDRPT maintains security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information to prevent unauthorized removal or alteration of data.
Website SecurityDRPT maintains security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to ensure that this service remains available to all users, and to prevent unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage. Information on individuals causing damage to the website will be traced and released to the appropriate legal bodies (such as the Virginia State Police) to investigate suspected or alleged criminal activity.
Copyright © 2018 All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy
